const charactersQuestions = [
    {
       "id":"1",
       "question":"In what land did Job live?",
       "optionOne":"Oz",
       "optionTwo":"Id",
       "optionThree":"Uz",
       "optionFour":"Ur",
       "correctAnswer":"Uz"
    },
    {
       "id":"2",
       "question":"How many children did Job lose in a storm?",
       "optionOne":"6",
       "optionTwo":"8",
       "optionThree":"10",
       "optionFour":"12",
       "correctAnswer":"10"
    },
    {
       "id":"3",
       "question":"What kind of disease struck Job?",
       "optionOne":"Leprosy",
       "optionTwo":"Blindness",
       "optionThree":"Madness",
       "optionFour":"Boils",
       "correctAnswer":"Boils"
    },
    {
       "id":"4",
       "question":"Who told Job in his troubles to curse God and die?",
       "optionOne":"His wife",
       "optionTwo":"Eliphaz",
       "optionThree":"Satan",
       "optionFour":"His servant",
       "correctAnswer":"His wife"
    },
    {
       "id":"5",
       "question":"Who attempted to comfort Job in his distress?",
       "optionOne":"His wife",
       "optionTwo":"His friends",
       "optionThree":"God",
       "optionFour":"No-one",
       "correctAnswer":"His friends"
    },
    {
       "id":"6",
       "question":"Which of these was not one of Job's friends?",
       "optionOne":"Zophar",
       "optionTwo":"Bildad",
       "optionThree":"Elihu",
       "optionFour":"Eliphaz",
       "correctAnswer":"Elihu"
    },
    {
       "id":"7",
       "question":"Job's friends kept vigil with him in silence for how long?",
       "optionOne":"24hours",
       "optionTwo":"3days",
       "optionThree":"7days",
       "optionFour":"40days",
       "correctAnswer":"7days"
    },
    {
       "id":"8",
       "question":"How much longer did Job live after his sufferings?",
       "optionOne":"85 years",
       "optionTwo":"100 years",
       "optionThree":"120 years",
       "optionFour":"140 years",
       "correctAnswer":"140 years"
    },
    {
       "id":"9",
       "question":"Who was Israel's firstborn son?",
       "optionOne":"Reuben",
       "optionTwo":"Joseph",
       "optionThree":"Benjamin",
       "optionFour":"Gog",
       "correctAnswer":"Saul"
    },
    {
       "id":"10",
       "question":"How many children did Israel have?",
       "optionOne":"5",
       "optionTwo":"7",
       "optionThree":"9",
       "optionFour":"12",
       "correctAnswer":"13"
    },
    {
       "id":"11",
       "question":"David had a daughter named what?",
       "optionOne":"Tamar",
       "optionTwo":"Maacah",
       "optionThree":"Abigail",
       "optionFour":"Hebron",
       "correctAnswer":"Bathsheba"
    },
    {
       "id":"12",
       "question":"Jabez prayed that the God of Israel would bless him and expand his borders. What did God do?",
       "optionOne":"Killed him",
       "optionTwo":"Made him king",
       "optionThree":"Sent armies against him",
       "optionFour":"Granted his request",
       "correctAnswer":"Ignored him"
    },
    {
       "id":"13",
       "question":"Who was John the Baptist's father?",
       "optionOne":"Thaddeus",
       "optionTwo":"Joseph",
       "optionThree":"Zechariah",
       "optionFour":"Malachi",
       "correctAnswer":"Zechariah"
    },
    {
       "id":"14",
       "question":"Who was John the Baptist's mother?",
       "optionOne":"Mary",
       "optionTwo":"Elisabeth",
       "optionThree":"Martha",
       "optionFour":"Rachel",
       "correctAnswer":"Elisabeth"
    },
    {
       "id":"15",
       "question":"What kind of clothes did John the Baptist wear?",
       "optionOne":"Camel'shair",
       "optionTwo":"Sheepskin",
       "optionThree":"Buffalohair",
       "optionFour":"Wovencloth",
       "correctAnswer":"Camel'shair"
    },
    {
       "id":"16",
       "question":"John the Baptist was how much older than Jesus?",
       "optionOne":"2 years",
       "optionTwo":"1 year",
       "optionThree":"6 months",
       "optionFour":"He was younger",
       "correctAnswer":"6 months"
    },
    {
       "id":"17",
       "question":"The relationship of Jesus to John the Baptist was:",
       "optionOne":"Brother",
       "optionTwo":"Cousin",
       "optionThree":"John was Jesus' Uncle",
       "optionFour":"NONE",
       "correctAnswer":"Cousin"
    },
    {
       "id":"18",
       "question":"What is the name of the river in which John the Baptist baptized people?",
       "optionOne":"Euphrates",
       "optionTwo":"Nile",
       "optionThree":"Jordan",
       "optionFour":"Tigris",
       "correctAnswer":"Jordan"
    },
    {
       "id":"19",
       "question":"John the Baptist was put in prison for declaring that Herod had broken what Law?",
       "optionOne":"Lying",
       "optionTwo":"Murder",
       "optionThree":"Violating the Sabbath",
       "optionFour":"Adultery",
       "correctAnswer":"Adultery"
    },
    {
       "id":"20",
       "question":"When Jesus heard that John the baptist had been arrested, where did he go?",
       "optionOne":"Jerusalem",
       "optionTwo":"Nazareth",
       "optionThree":"Galilee",
       "optionFour":"Bethany",
       "correctAnswer":"Galilee"
    },
    {
       "id":"21",
       "question":"Who asked God to bless him and enlarge his territory?",
       "optionOne":"Job",
       "optionTwo":"Jabez",
       "optionThree":"Jeremiah",
       "optionFour":"Isaiah",
       "correctAnswer":"Jabez"
    },
    {
       "id":"22",
       "question":"Who bought Joseph from the Midianite traders?",
       "optionOne":"Potiphar",
       "optionTwo":"Pharoah",
       "optionThree":"Hobab",
       "optionFour":"Raguel",
       "correctAnswer":"Potiphar"
    },
    {
       "id":"23",
       "question":"Who lied to the Holy Spirit and an apostle and died with her husband?",
       "optionOne":"MaryMagdalene",
       "optionTwo":"Sarah",
       "optionThree":"Sapphira",
       "optionFour":"Juniper",
       "correctAnswer":"Sapphira"
    },
    {
       "id":"24",
       "question":"Who refused to appear before her husband, the king, at his command?",
       "optionOne":"Esther",
       "optionTwo":"Vashti",
       "optionThree":"QueenofSheba",
       "optionFour":"Candace",
       "correctAnswer":"Vashti"
    },
    {
       "id":"25",
       "question":"Who climbed up into a sycomore tree to see Jesus?",
       "optionOne":"Matthew",
       "optionTwo":"Joseph of Arimathaea",
       "optionThree":"Simon, the Pharisee",
       "optionFour":"Zacchaeus",
       "correctAnswer":"Zacchaeus"
    },
    {
       "id":"26",
       "question":"Who offered the people a choice - Barabbas, or Jesus to be released?",
       "optionOne":"Herod",
       "optionTwo":"Pilate",
       "optionThree":"Caesar",
       "optionFour":"Herodias",
       "correctAnswer":"Pilate"
    },
    {
       "id":"27",
       "question":"Out of whom did Jesus cast seven devils?",
       "optionOne":"Pilate'swife",
       "optionTwo":"Martha",
       "optionThree":"Mary Magdalene",
       "optionFour":"Simon's mother",
       "correctAnswer":"Mary Magdalene"
    },
    {
       "id":"28",
       "question":"What prophetess told Barak to defeat Sisera and Jabin's army?",
       "optionOne":"Deborah",
       "optionTwo":"Abigail",
       "optionThree":"Rahab",
       "optionFour":"Jael",
       "correctAnswer":"Deborah"
    },
    {
       "id":"29",
       "question":"Jacob's wife Rachel died giving birth to whom?",
       "optionOne":"Joseph",
       "optionTwo":"Simeon",
       "optionThree":"Asher",
       "optionFour":"Benjamin",
       "correctAnswer":"Benjamin"
    },
    {
       "id":"30",
       "question":"Who was killed by three darts shot into his heart?",
       "optionOne":"Judah",
       "optionTwo":"Absalom",
       "optionThree":"Uzziah",
       "optionFour":"Goliath",
       "correctAnswer":"Absalom"
    },
    {
       "id":"31",
       "question":"What was the name of Judas' father?",
       "optionOne":"Jonah",
       "optionTwo":"Iscariot",
       "optionThree":"Alexander",
       "optionFour":"Simon",
       "correctAnswer":"Simon"
    },
    {
       "id":"32",
       "question":"How much was Judas Iscariot given to betray Jesus?",
       "optionOne":"20piecesofsilver",
       "optionTwo":"ATalentofgold",
       "optionThree":"30piecesofsilver",
       "optionFour":"100pence",
       "correctAnswer":"30piecesofsilver"
    },
    {
       "id":"33",
       "question":"What did Jesus give to Judas as a sign that he was to betray Him?",
       "optionOne":"Glass of wine",
       "optionTwo":"Bread",
       "optionThree":"Jar of honey",
       "optionFour":"Bag of coins",
       "correctAnswer":"Bread"
    },
    {
       "id":"34",
       "question":"How did Judas betray Jesus?",
       "optionOne":"Hepointed him out",
       "optionTwo":"He talked with him",
       "optionThree":"He held onto him",
       "optionFour":"He kissed him",
       "correctAnswer":"He kissed him"
    },
    {
       "id":"35",
       "question":"How did Judas, the betrayer, die?",
       "optionOne":"He was killed by Peter.",
       "optionTwo":"He hung himself.",
       "optionThree":"He was crucified.",
       "optionFour":"None",
       "correctAnswer":"He hung himself."
    },
    {
       "id":"36",
       "question":"What was the name of the field that was purchased with the betrayal money Judas returned?",
       "optionOne":"Corban",
       "optionTwo":"Golgotha",
       "optionThree":"Aceldama",
       "optionFour":"Gabbatha",
       "correctAnswer":"Aceldama"
    },
    {
       "id":"37",
       "question":"After Jesus' ascension, which two men were proposed to replace Judas?",
       "optionOne":"Joseph and Matthias",
       "optionTwo":"Philip and Nicanor",
       "optionThree":"Stephen and Paul",
       "optionFour":"Timon and Procorus",
       "correctAnswer":"Joseph and Matthias"
    },
    {
       "id":"38",
       "question":" Which one was finally chosen by the other eleven to replace Judas?",
       "optionOne":"Joseph",
       "optionTwo":"Paul",
       "optionThree":"Matthias",
       "optionFour":"Philip",
       "correctAnswer":"Matthias"
    },
    {
       "id":"",
       "question":"",
       "optionOne":"",
       "optionTwo":"",
       "optionThree":"",
       "optionFour":"",
       "correctAnswer":""
    }
];

export default charactersQuestions;